http://www.naco.org/naco-privacy-policy

Hire Quality Staff
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
NACo Privacy Policy
The National Association of Counties (NACo) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to NACo Web site and governs data collection and usage at all NACo sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the NACo Statement of Privacy. NACo is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.
Collection of your Personal Information
As an E-commerce Web site, NACo collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by NACo is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases. NACo does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.
As part of standard internet practice we collect the following information when you visit our sites:
Your IP address, a number automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the internet;
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
The Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site;
The date and time you visited this site
The pages you visit within the NACo site
NACo encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from NACo so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the NACo Web site.
Use of your Personal Information
NACo and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested.
NACo does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. NACo may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
NACo does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
NACo may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NACo or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NACo, including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NACo or the public.
Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which NACo or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. NACo abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control your Personal Information
NACo offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may notify us of your preferences by emailing info@naco.org. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records.
You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from NACo by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list
Security of your Personal Information
NACo is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through Verisign’s Payment Service.
Changes to this Statement
NACo will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how NACo will use your personal information, NACo will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. NACo encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NACo is protecting your information.
The National Association of Counties (NACo) is committed to protecting your privacy.
2018-04-02
Basic page
2020-10-27
The National Association of Counties (NACo) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to NACo Web site and governs data collection and usage at all NACo sites and services; it does not apply to other online or offline sites, products or services. Please read the NACo Statement of Privacy. NACo is a general audience web site, intended for users of all ages. Personal information of all users is collected, used and disclosed as described in this Statement of Privacy.
Collection of your Personal Information
As an E-commerce Web site, NACo collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Information collected by NACo is used solely for the purpose of billing and shipping your online purchases. NACo does not collect any information about your computer hardware and software.
As part of standard internet practice we collect the following information when you visit our sites:
Your IP address, a number automatically assigned to your computer when you are using the internet;
The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
The Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our site;
The date and time you visited this site
The pages you visit within the NACo site
NACo encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from NACo so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. We are not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the NACo Web site.
Use of your Personal Information
NACo and its operational service partners collect and use your personal information to process product orders and deliver the products requested.
NACo does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. NACo may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personal information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party.
We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. We will only provide those companies the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information and are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.
NACo does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
NACo may access and/or disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on NACo or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of NACo, including its Web site; or (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of NACo or the public.
Personal information collected on this site may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which NACo or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. NACo abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control your Personal Information
NACo offers its customers choices for the collection, use and sharing of personal information. You may notify us of your preferences by emailing info@naco.org. Please be sure to provide complete account information so we can identify you in our records.
You may also stop the delivery of future promotional e-mail from NACo by responding directly to any email you receive with a request to remove you from the mailing list
Security of your Personal Information
NACo is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through Verisign’s Payment Service.
Changes to this Statement
NACo will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. If there are material changes to this Statement or in how NACo will use your personal information, NACo will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. NACo encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how NACo is protecting your information.
NACo
© 2019 National Association of Counties | 660 North Capitol Street NW | Suite 400 | Washington, DC | 20001 | Phone: 202.393.6226
Website built on Drupal by Taoti Creative | Privacy Policy
